# Seng Hao Yeoh

Greater Brisbane Area



leoricyeoh@hotmail.com



0466546804



linkedin.com/in/seng-hao-yeoh-a1ba78195

## Summary

I pride myself in being a Hardworking and Creative worker in a creative, inspiring and marketing teams. I love balancing the creative mind and the hard work to produce results. Brand development, creative marketing and data analysing are my passion.

Challenges and constant learning has driven me to think outside of the box. I love to be challenged, and challenge others to bring out the best of each others' abilities. Let's connect and see what we can do together.

Over the past few months, I have helped BRNA to increase their interactivity on their social media platform. I have also helped Domino's St Lucia Store to manage their end of the day finance.

My area of expertise includes digital marketing, infographics, advertising, social media, marketing, scheduling, team building, leadership, and analytics.

### **Experience**

# Marketing Assistant

Sunway Total Rubber

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Created a product catalogue for the company with precision.

Created a brochure for marketing purposes.



#### Shift runner

Domino's

Jun 2019 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Manage a team of employees when the manager is not in the store.

Open and Close store, manage opening and closing balance for the day.

#### Strategy and Commercial Intern

#### **PETRONAS**

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022 (5 months)

During this internship, I am responsible for building the Performance Dashboard of Petronas Brisbane (PAPL) using PowerBI from scratch which includes cleaning the data and setting up the excel sheet for long term use.

As a result, I am able to assist the team in building the dashboard for long run and figures will be updated automatically.



#### **Mechanical Technician**

Strong-Lift Engineering

Nov 2017 - Mar 2018 (5 months)
Forkllift services and maintenance

#### **Education**

The University of Queensland

Master's degree, Information Technology Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

The University of Queensland

Bachelor of Business Management, Marketing 2019 - 2021

Sunway College

Australian Matriculation , Science 2018 - 2018

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Social Marketing Certification - Hootsuite 32008096

### **Skills**

Web Development • Python (Programming Language) • English • Marketing • Market Planning • Social Media Marketing • Marketing • Content Marketing